sportspower.com 2010-12-03

# Privacy Policy - The Active Network

Active recognizes that privacy is important. This Privacy Policy applies to all of the websites and products owned and/or operated by The Active Network, Inc. and its subsidiary and affiliated companies (collectively “Active”) unless expressly noted otherwise. The majority of Active’s websites are intended for a general audience and this policy describes our general use of information. For Active’s websites that may be used by a younger audience, more specific policies applicable to children under the age of 13 will be located on each such site.

**Collection and Use of Information**

Some of Active’s websites permit users, subject further to Active’s online terms of use, to register for events or programs, request information, enter contests, vote in polls or otherwise express opinions or submit comments. As part of such use, you may be asked to register for a free ID and password and to provide certain personally identifying information such as name, address, phone number, email address, birth date, ZIP code, gender, personal interests and credit card information for transactions. Active uses your information to perform transactions, deliver services or information you have requested, and offer you products and services from Active and our trusted partners, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you. Active also uses your information to contact you when necessary for customer service purposes. We may combine your information that we have with information we obtain from business partners or third parties to provide you with a better product or Active experience. Active may use information relating to your visit or use of our websites, or information you provide to us, for market research purposes in order to continually improve the product and services that Active delivers to you.

If you choose to submit content for publication we may publish your screen name and other information as provided by you or to personalize your user experience. If you register for a competitive event, your name, event entry identification, and interim and final event time results may be made publicly available on any Active website. 

Active receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Active cookies (small pieces of information stored by your browser), and the page(s) you request. Active uses this information to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

When Active does share your information with our subsidiaries, affiliated companies and trusted businesses or persons, we require that these parties agree to process such information based on our direction and in compliance with appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 

Active also displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Third party advertisers (including ad-serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click targeted ads meet the targeting criteria. However, Active does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted advertisement.

Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, it is Active's policy not to distribute to third parties any personally identifying information about you without your consent (usually communicated through either an “opt-out” or “opt-in” notification or mechanism). Upon obtaining your consent, Active may provide access to or otherwise disclose your personally identifying information to third parties. However, we may aggregate certain personally identifying information - meaning that the information from many Active users is grouped together in a way that does not disclose the personal information of any particular user – without your consent. 

You may choose not to submit certain personal information while on our websites, in such instances Active may not be able to provide you with certain services.

If you are using our services to register for an event, program or to purchase a third party product, Active shares the personal information you provide to applicable third party(ies) to fulfill your request. Each such party operates independently from Active and maintains its own privacy and security policy. Active bears no responsibility from the activities of any such third party to whom Active provides information to process your request and you should contact those third parties directly regarding your preferences for the use of your personal information.

**Legal Disclosures**

Active may release your personal information to third parties: (a) in order to comply with a valid legal requirement such as in compliance with any law, regulation, search warrant subpoena or court order; or (b) in special cases, when we believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding any illegal or unauthorized activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person or violations of our Terms of Use. 

**Information Security**

Active has established and maintains reasonable security procedures to protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of your personally identifiable information, including the use of secure socket layer (SSL) and encryption methods. We regularly evaluate our data collection, storage and processing practices and security to guard against unauthorized access to our systems. You can help to protect your information by safeguarding your Active password and using caution and discretion when posting information on public areas of the sites. 

Although Active uses commercially reasonable efforts to safeguard your information, transmissions made by means of the Internet cannot be fully secure in all instances and we cannot guarantee that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is not consistent with this Privacy Policy.

More information on Active’s security can be found at: <http://www.activenetwork.com/security.htm>.

**Unsubscribe**

If addition, if at anytime, you no longer want us to send you any regular communications, you may “opt-out” of such future communications, clicking on the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of the newsletter or email. To “opt-out” of products, programs, services, or offers from our trusted partners, please contact [privacy@activenetwork.com](mailto:privacy@activenetwork.com). 

**Contact Us**

Active regularly reviews its practices regarding personally identifiable information and this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions, comments or concerns, please contact us at:

Attn: Privacy Officer  
The Active Network, Inc.  
10182 Telesis Court  
San Diego, CA 92121

**Changes**

Active may transfer the personal information collected under this Privacy Policy to a third party in the event of a transfer of ownership such as a merger, acquisition or any form of sale of the majority of the assets of Active. 

Active reserves the right to modify or supplement this privacy policy at anytime without any prior notice to you. If we make any changes, we will update the Active websites and this Privacy Policy to include such change. Please regularly review this Privacy Policy to keep up to date with any changes that may affect your use of the Active Websites. Your continued use of the Active websites once the revised privacy policy has been posted on the websites affirms your agreement to such changes.
